CRISTINA DOMINGUES MARIANO SCHIAPPA PIETRA

Lisbon · 914819753 · 18-06-1998

cristina.pietra@hotmail.com | linkedin.com/in/cristina-pietra

Highly motivated and always eager to learn. Started working at a very early age while studying, which allowed me to gain experience in many areas. Some of those areas include customer support, sales, finance, design and programming.

Native portuguese and fluent in english after spending 3 years working in England.

EXPERIENCE

2021 - 2023 PORTUGAL

FUTURES TRADER, INDEPENDENT

- Handled buy and sell transactions for financial instruments.
- Analyzed market trends and conditions.
- Created detailed financial plans.
- Planned evidence-based strategies to manage transactional risk.
- Employed multiple trading techniques to maximise profits.
- Automated strategies

2020 – 2020 UNITED KINGDOM

CUSTOMER ASSISTANT, HALFORDS

- Offered advice on product selection for enhanced levels of support and service.
- Provided fast checkout service with high levels of customer care and transaction speed.
- Carried out regular quality checks to ensure displayed products were in good, saleable condition.
- Handled cash and card payments with accuracy.
- Tracked orders and processed refunds for new and existing customers.
- Provided information regarding warranties, promos and loyalty programs to enhance customer satisfaction.
- Registered and updated accurate customer information on database.

2020 – 2020 UNITED KINGDOM

CELL PHONE TECHNICIAN, REDEEM

- Tested functionality of mobile devices.
- Diagnosed battery problems to determine root of cause.
- Utilized in-store POS system to track repair tickets.
- Performed quality control measures to gauge quality control.

2019 - 2019 PORTUGAL

PIZZA MAKER, TELEPIZZA

- Expertly hand-stretched pizza dough and added toppings according to orders, maintaining strict attention to detail.
- Handled phone and in-store orders to meet service targets.
- Completed comprehensive closing and cleaning checklists.
- Sterilized kitchen equipment, plates and utensils to maintain clean environment.
- Safely operated pizza oven and other kitchen equipment according to manufacturer instructions.

2016 - 2018 PORTUGAL

CUSTOMER ASSISTANT, PETALA AROMAS

- Offered advice on product selection for enhanced levels of support and service.
- Operating a till system.
- Work alongside colleagues on shop floor.
- Handled cash and card payments with accuracy.
- Performed daily opening and closing functions and inventory management.
- Created attractive visual merchandising and shop window displays.

2016 - 2018 PORTUGAL

CUSTOMER ASSISTANT, PETALA STUDIO

- Carried out regular quality checks to ensure displayed products were in good, saleable condition.
- Operating a till system.
- Handled requests with friendly, knowledgeable service and support, continually achieving positive customer feedback.
- Performed daily opening and closing functions and inventory management.
- Offered prompt solutions to maintain customer satisfaction.

2015 - 2015 PORTUGAL

CALL CENTER OPERATOR AND SALES ASSISTANT, THERAPIA

- Door-to-door sales.
- Used charismatic sales strategy to engage passing customers in outdoor market atmosphere.
- Demonstrated or explained details and features of sale items.
- Successfully generated new business via telephone sales, achieving profit growth targets.
- Attended regular product training to enhance customer advice.
- Trained junior agents on customer service excellence, boosting customer satisfaction rates.

2013 - 2014 PORTUGAL

FLYER DISTRIBUTOR, REMAX

- Offered flexible working hours.
- Completed distribution tasks quickly to meet volume targets.
- Employed knowledge of distribution area to optimize routes and increase productivity.

EDUCATION

2017 - 2019

VIDEOGAMES BACHELOR'S DEGREE, LUSOFONA UNIVERSITY

2013 - 2016

HIGHSCHOOL, CARCAVELOS SCHOOL

LANGUAGES

- English Fluent
- Portuguese Native

- Spanish Beginner
- German Beginner

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- Basic programming knowledge (python, c#, c++, php, golang, html, dart, etc.)
- Great knowledge of photo, video, 3D modeling and sound edition (Photoshop, Premiere Pro, Sony Vegas, Blender, Zbrush, Audacity, etc.
- Currently taking a Cybersecurity online course

- Automating Trading Strategies
- Excelent knowledge of Trading Softwares (Ninjatrader, Interactive Brokers)
- Great knowledge of Excel, Word and Powerpoint.

ACTIVITIES

- Trading
- Oil Painting/ Digital painting
- Programming

- Gym
- Gaming
- Taking care of my cats